fusionradio.fm 2012-06-05

# .:: Fusion Radio ::. Internet Dance Radio | Chicago | San Francisco

| 

Our Commitment To Privacy   
At Fusion Radio we are heavily committed to your privacy.  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.  
  
The Information We Collect:   
Your computer IP address  
Your city/state, zip or location  
Your computer operating system  
This information is used for solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals. ****This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on **Fusion Radio** website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: **  
**Name:  
Address:  
Email address:  
Phone number:  
The Way We Use Information:   
**To process your order with our company along with developing an effective marketing plan to reach more viewers.   Your information in no shape or form, will be distributed or sold to any third party member.   
**  
Our Commitment To Data Security   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:   
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

How To Contact Us:   
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 

**1.888.491.0169** or send us an email at **fusion@fusionradio.fm**  

|
